# Juan Sebastian Caicedo Alfonso

Software developer | Electronic engineer

# **Projects**

#### Order Management Application - video

December 2021 - December 2021

Full interface and restful api that handles the process of creating and processing orders for a retail company. Learned **React, Flask, html, javascript, css, bootstrap, sqlalchemy, and mysql**. It allows the user to log in, log out, create, display, and delete orders and clients.

#### Know your business - AltspaceVR MRE

November 2021 - December 2021

Mixed reality extension for the AltspaceVR platform. It uses Nufi's apis to allow users to do taxpayers and trademarks research in Mexico's archives in a 3D environment. Learned **typescript** and **altspace MRE SDK**.

#### Know your business - Web App

September 2021 - October 2021

Web application that uses Nufi's apis to retrieve information from any company. Learned **c#, and ASP.NET** as back-end and front-end framework. It uses an implementation of Model-View-Controller architecture (MVC).

#### Conway's Game of Life Simulator

June 2021 - June 2021

GUI developed in python simulating Conway's Game of Life.

#### Simple Shell

May 2021 - June 2021

Command-line interpreter made from scratch in C language for Unix systems

# **Experience**

#### Software Developer - at Nufi

Jan 2022 - Present

Developing proof of concepts and new products for the company to work and sell, answering directly to the CEO. Developed a whatsapp chatbot that retrieves info from public ids through OCR and delivers a full report of the people. Developed in **node.js**, **express and selenium**.

#### Software Developer - Internship at Nufi

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

Built a "Know your business" (KYB) web app. Improved the user experience from the previous application the company was implementing. Designed a **restful API**, which when implemented, increased the legibility and the amount of the data presented to the clients.

#### Math and Programing Teacher

May 2017 - Present

Autonomous teacher to students all around the world. Taught 12 students per week identifying their specific way of learning and creating dynamic and fun lessons while getting a student's rate of hiring again of 97%.

### Education

#### Full stack software developer, Holberton School

February 2021 - November 2021

Holberton School is a peer-learning, project-guided, and self-learning-based full-stack software engineering school.

#### Electronic Engineer, Universidad del Valle

2010 - 2016

Electronic engineering bachelor

### **Details**



+57 317 858 4597



sebas93cay@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/sebscaicedo



github.com/Sebas93cay

## **Profile**

Software developer with a keen sense of detail and optimization. Thanks to my eagerness to learn and research I've been able to develop different solutions for the Fintech Industry, including integration of automated messaging services, API design architecture, web scraping with Selenium, and data manipulation.

I like to learn and use clean architectures, agile development methodologies, and front-end frameworks like React to build stunning user-oriented platforms.

### **Technical Skills**

- Javascript
- Clean Architecture
- Python
- HTML
- CSS
- React.js
- Flask
- Vue
- Node.js
- MySQL
- GitC

# Languages

Spanish: Native

• English: Conversational - Proficient